RAKHA VIANTONI PRASTYA

rakha@arvipi.com

github.com/rakhaviantoni

INFO

Birthday 1997-07-14 Languages Native: Bahasa

Fluent: English

Based on DKI Jakarta, Indonesia Phone +62 896 322 48327

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 (Expected)

President University (in English)

B.Sc. in Information Technology (in Progress)
Worked on a variety of programming projects in teams.

2012 - 2015

2 Vocational High School

Software Engineering

Basic Java, VB, & Website Programming.

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2017 - Feb 2018

BCA Learning Institute

Vendor

Worked on making new E-learning using Moodle and setting up the server.

Jan 2016 - Jan 2018

President University Student Council

Web Developer

Student legislative body. Responsible for creating and managing the website either for internal (AdminPUSC) or external (Frontpage, Online Borrowing System & Aspiration Form) needs.

May 2017 - Jun 2017

CV. Simply Digital Studio

Web Developer Intern

Helped to develop several on-running projects using Codelgniter.

Nov 2013 - Jan 2014

Ikatan Ahli Teknik Penyehatan dan Teknik Lingkungan Jakarta

Internship Staff

Helped on documenting stuff, etc. Created a modern looking website for IATPI using Joomla.

PROFILE

A passionate Web Developer with 3+ years of experience in modern website development. Proficient with Laravel and Vue combination that has implemented on creating some projects. Have experienced with famous Mobile Programmings like Android Studio and Ionic. Love to create a scalable website with modern features. Able to work under deadline independently or as a part of a team.

SKILLS

Languages: Strong: PHP

Knowledgeable: Java, Ruby, Python, Go
WebDev: Strong: Laravel, JS, jQuery, Vue, Sass, Ionic

Knowledgeable: Rails, Django, ExpressJS, PWA, Angular, React, React Native

Database: Strong: MySQL, Postgre SQL

Knowledgeable: Firebase, MongoDB, Redis

Others: Arduino, IoT, Linux, NodeJS, NPM, Git,

Gulp, Webpack, Yarn

PROJECTS

Astra Motor Referral System (Laravel, Vue, Pusher) Arvipi-System: Simple CMS (Laravel, Vue, Pusher)

M-PUSC: Progressive Web App (Vuetify)

Arpha: Simple POS (Laravel, JS, jQuery) *Based on

Arvipi-System Alpha Version

Polygon & Polyline Creator: Linked List (Visual Basic)

Sepik: Text to Speech Mobile App (Ionic)

PYLC's Website: Event's Registration System with

 $auto-generated\ Invoice\ Letter\ (Laravel)$

PUSC's Website: AdminPUSC, Frontpage, Online Borrowing System & Aspiration Form (*Laravel*, *Vue*)

FindMe: Friends Location Tracker App (Android Studio)

Department's Data Application (Visual Basic)

REFERENCES

Ronny Juwono, S.Pd., MT.

Lecturer, President University ronny@president.ac.id

Nadia P. Ayuningtyas

HCD Department, PT Astra International Tbk-Honda nadia.ayuningtyas@hso.astra.co.id